{"data":[{"question":"What is your opinion of Mark? \" I ___ him a genius\"","a":"consider","b":"say","c":"understand","d":"look at","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Consider somebody\/something (to be) something: to think of someone or something in a particular way or to have a particular opinion","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"I believe ___ due to mistaken views of the world.","a":"this unhappiness are","b":"to be this unhappiness","c":"this be unhappiness","d":"this unhappiness to be","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Believe sbd\/sth to be sbd\/sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Are you going to leave ___ ?","a":"the open windows","b":"the windows opened","c":"open the windows","d":"the windows open","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Leave something open\/empty\/untidy etc: to let something remain in a particular state, position, or condition","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Is dinner ready? \" No, mother is ___ it ready now.\"","a":"doing","b":"cooking","c":"getting","d":"preparing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Get: to prepare food or a meal","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Last night, in a radio address, the President urged us ___ the Red Cross\"","a":"to support","b":"support","c":"supporting","d":"supported","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Urge somebody to do something","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The president was very angry because Mr. Brown ___.","a":"had permitted the students to use the instruments","b":"had let the students to use the instruments","c":"allowed the students use the instruments","d":"had allowed the students using the instruments","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Permit\/allow sbd to do sth\n- Let sbd do sth\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"A later phase of land reform, called \" Land to the Tiller,\" enables peasants ___ up to 175 acres of the land.","a":"to buy","b":"to buying","c":"buying","d":"buy","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Enable sbd to do sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"I like Nancy but I do not like _________.","a":"her sing","b":"her singing","c":"she sing","d":"she singing","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Like + Verb_ing\/noun \n- Singing (noun): the activity of producing musical sounds with your voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Isn't that our plane? \" Yes, let's go. Maybe we'll find Tom ___ at the gate.\"","a":"to have waiting for us","b":"to have waited for us","c":"waited for us","d":"waiting for us","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n- Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb_ing : you find \/see or watch part of the action","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"When I returned home, I found the window ___ and something ___.","a":"break, steal","b":"broken, stolen","c":"breaking, stealing","d":"to break, to steal","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Passive voice with some verbs : Find\/ see\/ watch...:\nFind\/see\/watch + Object + Past participle","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"64","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"}]}